(Verse 1)
Caught between the pull and flight,
Fire below and stars in sight,
I was born from dust and flame,
Built to break and rise again.
(Pre-Chorus)
Every fall just feeds the climb,
Every scar rewrites the time,
I’m not bound by what they see,
I’m the force that set me free.
(Chorus)
Gravity won’t hold me down,
Sky’s my heart, the earth’s my sound,
Every motion breaks the chain,
I’m the storm that breathes again.
(Verse 2)
Hands of light, the world unfolds,
Silver dreams and fields of gold,
Every turn, I feel it still —
The universe bends to my will.
(Bridge)
Let the cosmos spin in fire,
Fuel the pulse of my desire,
If time should fall, I’ll still be
found,
Where the echoes shake the ground.
(Finale)
Gravity won’t hold me down,
Every loss becomes my crown,
I was never made to stay —
I was born to break away.