I rise in the hush before the storm can
speak,
Gold in my veins, fire under my feet.
Every breath is a drum, every step is a
crown,
I was made for the sky, I was forged for
the sound.
I’ve walked on the edges where the brave
don’t go,
Where the night pulls close and the cold
winds blow.
I’ve carried the weight that could break
a spine,
Turned every scar to a battle sign.
You can’t dim a sun that was born to ign
ite,
Can’t drown a tide when it’s already
night.
I’m the spark in the dark, I’m the storm
set free,
When the gates swing wide, they’ll
remember me.
I sit on a throne of thunder,
Every strike’s a hymn, every roar’s my
number.
Raise your hands, feel the heavens
break,
We were born for the fire, let the whole
world shake.
I’ve seen crowns fall to the dust and
fade,
Seen kings lose thrones they thought
they made.
But I don’t bow and I don’t chase gold,
I am the story the prophets told.
My blood is a river, my voice a flame,
I’m the echo that carries a holy name.
Every fall was a step, every step was a
climb,
Now the peak is mine, and the bell will
chime.
I sit on a throne of thunder,
Every strike’s a hymn, every roar’s my
number.
Raise your hands, feel the heavens
break,
We were born for the fire, let the whole
world shake.
Leader: Can you feel it in your chest?
Choir: Yes we can! Yes we can!
Leader: Will you stand through the test?
Leader: When the night turns red and the
sky rains light—
All: We will rise, we will fight, we
will burn so bright!
I sit on a throne of thunder,
Every strike’s a hymn, every roar’s my
number.
Raise your hands, feel the heavens
break,
We were born for the fire, let the whole
world shake.
This is the sound of the crown I claim,
Written in lightning, carved in flame.