(Verse 1)
No fear, no weight on me,
I’m moving faster than memory,
Skies unfold, the night ignites,
The world resets beneath my lights.
(Pre-Chorus)
Can’t stop, can’t fade,
I was built from fire and shade,
Every wall just turns to sound,
When I lift off from the ground.
(Chorus)
I’m running at lightspeed, burning the
cold,
Breaking the limits I used to hold,
No gravity, no chain, no past,
Just the pulse of forever — at last.
(Verse 2)
Echoes trail where I have been,
Gold dust falls from oxygen,
If I fall, I fall in flame,
And rise again, without a name.
(Bridge)
Let the system chase the spark,
I’m the flash that lights the dark,
Time bends back, I’m never gone,
I *am* the road that time runs on.
(Finale)
Through the chaos, through the speed,
I found peace in what I need,
Every breath — a supernova creed,
I was born to run — at lightspeed.