(VERSE 1)
No sparks now — just lines and angles,
noise burned off with the old entangles.
Heart still beat but it don't gamble,
mind cut clean like it solved the puzzle.
I don't flinch when the pressure stare,
already cracked — what's left to scare?
Silence thick but it's breathable air,
every move measured, nothing spare.
(PRE-CHORUS)
Stillness — sharpened edge,
I don't rush, I step correct.
Stillness — loaded breath,
I don't swing, I intercept.
Stillness — weaponized,
calm so cold it reorganize.
Stillness — that's the shift,
when survival turn into discipline.
(VERSE 2)
Used to think force meant raising voice,
now I see power is fewer choice.
Every word land like it got a point,
I don't waste breath — I deploy.
World still loud but it pass me by,
I move straight through like a narrowed eye.
You hear chaos — I hear reply,
pattern visible when the fear don't cry.
(BRIDGE)
I don't freeze.
I align.
I don't fight.
I decide.
(CHORUS)
Stillness — sharpened edge,
I don't rush, I step correct.
Stillness — loaded breath,
I don't swing, I intercept.
Stillness — weaponized,
calm so cold it reorganize.