Mmm… yeah…
Step into the room and the floor turns
gold,
Every heartbeat telling me to take
control.
They can dim the stage but they can’t
dim me,
I was born for the moment, I was made to
be free.
Drums in my chest like a war in bloom,
Every step I take is a throne in the
room.
Skin like fire, voice like rain,
Every move a prayer, every note a chain
Breaking loose in the dark till the light breaks through,
I’m the wind in the storm, I’m the sun
in the hue.
Every crown they took, I built my own,
With the love, with the fight, with the
seeds I’ve sown.
This is my crown of light, I wear it
high,
Shining through the fire, I electrify.
They can try to break my stride, I won’t
fall,
Hear the sound of my name when I stand tall.
They wrote my ending in invisible ink,
But the words came alive when I started
to think.
Every "no" they threw was a brick in the
wall,
But I danced on the top, never feared
the fall.
I’ve been the flame, I’ve been the
spark,
I’ve been the lantern in the endless
dark.
Now my song is the flood that can’t be
denied,
Every note a wave, every wave a tide.
This is my crown of light, I wear it
high,
Shining through the fire, I electrify.
They can try to break my stride, I won’t
fall,
Hear the sound of my name when I stand tall.
Oh, you feel that heat when the truth
walks in,
Every shadow fades when the soul begins.
We don’t bow, we don’t break, we don’t
run away,
We just lift up the sky till it shines
like day.
This is my crown of light, I wear it
high,
Shining through the fire, I electrify.
They can try to break my stride, I won’t
fall,
Hear the sound of my name when I stand tall.
Mmm… my crown… my crown of light…
I wear it high…