(INTRO)
Nobody stopped.
The universe doesn't pause.
So I moved with it.
(VERSE 1)
Crowds still moving when I step outside,
systems humming like they never died.
I'm not special — I just stayed alive,
learned how to move when the lanes collide.
People got routes, people got roles,
everyone circling something they know.
I don't fight it, I let it unfold,
find my line in the pull and go.
(PRE-CHORUS)
In orbit —
not lost, not free.
this is where I need to be.
In orbit —
close enough to feel the heat,
far enough to still breathe.
In orbit —
not lost, not free.
this is where I need to be.
In orbit —
close enough to feel the heat,
far enough to still breathe.
(VERSE 2)
I see hands building what eyes don't show,
quiet work in a constant flow.
No applause when the system holds,
just motion proving that it knows.
I don't drift, I don't run ahead,
I match the pace of what's being said.
Universe loud, but it don't beg,
it keeps turning — so I step in.
We don't lead.
We don't wait.
We align.
We rotate.
(CHORUS)
In orbit —
not lost, not free.
this is where I need to be.
In orbit —
close enough to feel the heat,
far enough to still breathe.
(CHORUS)
In orbit —
not lost, not free.
this is where I need to be.
In orbit —
close enough to feel the heat,
far enough to still breathe.