They told me pay the fee,
Fifty months, maybe a hundred, just to
breathe.
Call it honor, call it pride,
But it feels like chains dressed up in
white.
Bank account bleeding in the name of a vow,
Triple the expenses, who’s laughing now?
Voices in my ear, say “live like this,
not that,”
But no matter what I give, they say it
ain’t enough back.
Is it love or illusion, a contract for
pain?
Or a ticket to a circus where the clowns
wear rings?
If freedom costs less than forever in debt,
Then I’ll take the silence, keep my dignity instead.
Price of love — too high, I can’t buy.
All these rules, just a cage in
disguise.
If the measure of my heart is the weight
of my gold,
I’d rather die free than be bartered and
sold.
They say it’s for sex, they say it’s for
life,
But the math don’t add up to joy or
light.
If keeping someone close means I’m
breaking my spine,
Then maybe love’s a prison I’ll never
sign.
What if I want a partner, not a chain?
What if I want the fire without the
pain?
What if I’d give my soul for someone
true —
But not my freedom, not my truth?
Price of love — too high, I can’t buy.
All these rules, just a cage in
disguise.
If the measure of my heart is the weight
of my gold,
I’d rather die free than be bartered and
sold.
Keep your illusion, keep your crown,
I’ll keep my dignity underground.
Love should lift, not bleed me dry,
I won’t trade my wings just to say
goodbye.