From the dirt to the dawn, I ignite with a roar,
Kicked the coffin wide open, now I’m back for more.
Every step’s a spark, every breath’s a flame,
Put respect on my rise, they remember the name.
I burn fear to smoke, turn pain into gold,
I’m the chapter they whisper but never get told.
Every scar’s a medal, every loss a win,
I’m the storm in the fire, let the uprising begin.
From ashes to anthems, we rise, we rise,
No chains, no ceilings, just skies, skies, skies.
From ashes to anthems, we fight, we fight,
Hands up, hearts loud, all night, all night!
I’m the heat in the heartbeat, the bass in your chest,
When the world said “quit,” I just laughed at the test.
I’m the light in the blackout, the crown in the smoke,
If you’re waiting for a savior, here’s the one they spoke.
I don’t beg for the throne, I just take the seat,
Every bar’s built in fire, every line’s concrete.
Legends ain’t born, nah, legends get made,
In the furnace of the fight where the brave don’t fade.
From ashes to anthems, we rise, we rise,
No chains, no ceilings, just skies, skies, skies.
From ashes to anthems, we fight, we fight,
Hands up, hearts loud, all night, all night!
Sing it for the ones who fell,
Sing it for the ones who burned,
We carry their names in the beat,
Till every tide has turned.
Rise! Rise! Rise!
Light it up! Light it up!
From the dust! From the dust!
We don’t break! We combust!
Yeah, we’re phoenix-born, with our hearts on fire,
Every dream we lost only takes us higher.
From the dirt to the dawn, hear the battle choir,
Ashes to anthems — this is our empire.
From ashes to anthems, we rise, we rise,
No chains, no ceilings, just skies, skies, skies.
From ashes to anthems, we fight, we fight,
Hands up, hearts loud, all night, all night!