(Verse 1)
Top hat tilt, shoes so clean,
Froggy Frog back on the scene.
Brass band bumpin’, moonlight glow,
he snaps once — the rhythm goes!
Green tie, gold ring, yeah he got that zing,
tail suit shine, hear the jukebox sing.
(Chorus / Drop)
Ribbit-ribbit, swing that thing,
hop to the beat like a boomerang wing.
Froggy Frog in the neon night,
jump so smooth, feel so right.
(Verse 2)
He don’t drive, he glides on sound,
spinning through clubs underground.
Girls in pearls, boys in blues,
Froggy Frog got electric shoes.
(Bridge / Rap-speak)
Tap two times and the floor ignites,
horns go crazy in strobe-light nights.
“Stay cool, stay loose,” he grins so
wide —
the frog’s in town, enjoy the ride.
(Final Chorus)
Ribbit-ribbit, turn it up,
fill your glass and raise that cup.
Hop to the future, past collide —
Froggy Frog, electro pride!
(Outro)
One snap, two claps, fade in brass,
the frog still dancin’ — class on class.