Yo, step through the glass —
反射 (hansha) hits back like a bassline
blast.
Petals in the air, light bends like a
sin,
Welcome to the mirror garden — let the
story begin.
I’m the glasswalker, bending every
reflection,
Flipping universes in a single
direction.
花が咲く (hana ga saku) where the beat drops
twice,
Parallel paths, rollin’ mirrored dice.
Shards of the moon in the koi pond shimmer,
Truth cuts deep in the silver-glass glimmer.
Every step’s a glitch, every move’s a code,
I’m the gardener of echoes on a mirrored
road.
鏡の庭 (kagami no niwa) — where the real
collides,
Infinite doors in the place that hides.
Step in once and you’ll never come back,
I’m the phoenix in the glass with a
flame on track.
Yo, I spit kanji like they’re ninja
stars,
Cutting through lies, breaking prison
bars.
影が踊る (kage ga odoru) when the bassline
drops,
Every rhyme’s a blossom that the timeline crops.
I plant seeds in the cracks of the
frame,
Watch them bloom in the heat of the
game.
The mirror don’t lie but it talks in
code,
If you read between the lines, you can
change the mode.
鏡の庭 (kagami no niwa) — where the real
collides,
Infinite doors in the place that hides.
Step in once and you’ll never come back,
I’m the phoenix in the glass with a
flame on track.
Bend the hourglass, break the hands of
time.
Every petal’s a key, every stem’s a map,
And the garden’s the stage where I lay
my trap.
Yo, reflection bends, perception blends,
This is where beginnings twist into
ends.
The mirror is the mic, and the beat’s
the seed,
In the garden of infinity — I plant what
you need.