(VERSE 1)
Pressure in my chest made a hairline split,
whole damn world tried to box my wit.
Voice went quiet but the pulse went lit,
crack in the mind, now the thoughts don't fit.
Didn't ask life for a script or a guide,
I just felt steel start forming inside.
Fear took one step back when I tried,
courage found room where the fracture applied.
(PRE-CHORUS)
That fissure — turned me clean,
cut my noise till the core went mean.
That fissure — split unseen,
broke my doubt with a silent beam.
That fissure — cold routine,
made my calm into gasoline.
That fissure — shift machine,
I made pain into discipline.
(VERSE 2)
Everything snapped but I stayed intact,
mind rearranged like a silent pact.
Truth got loud when the lies got cracked,
I saw who I am when the mask collapsed.
Step by step with a brand-new stance,
old hesitation never stood a chance.
Life threw heat but I learned to advance,
fractured once, now I cut through trance.
(BRIDGE)
Quiet break… loud result.
One small fault… made me adult.
(CHORUS)
That fissure — turned me clean,
cut my noise till the core went mean.
That fissure — split unseen,
broke my doubt with a silent beam.
That fissure — shift machine,
I made pain into gasoline.