If the divine wore skin and bones…
Where would they walk?
Would they sit in marble halls…
Or sleep under broken walls?
Maybe they’d show up barefoot,
Dust on their clothes, truth in their throat,
Not a crown, not a throne, just a hunger
For justice that burns like smoke.
Maybe they’d be in the camps,
Where the ground shakes when the sky
drops fire,
Holding a child who don’t know why
Their only lullaby is the sound of sirens.
Would you allow this? On your kid’s bed?
Would you excuse it? If it was your
blood shed?
Aren’t we cousins, same tree, same
roots,
Adam and Eve, yeah, the story’s in the
fruit.
If flesh carried love unshaken,
Would we embrace it or break it?
Would we listen or fake it?
Or crucify truth when we can’t take it?
They’d be found in the alleys,
Not in palaces with gates,
Feeding mouths the world abandoned,
Calling out the hand of hate.
Would you allow this? On your kid’s bed?
Would you excuse it? If it was your
blood shed?
Aren’t we cousins, same tree, same
roots,
Adam and Eve, yeah, the story’s in the
fruit.
This is not religion.
This is not war.
This is children crying
Behind shattered doors.
This is silence screaming
From a world gone numb.
This is distant cousins
Forgetting where they’re from.
If the sacred wore skin,
It would bleed like ours,
It would sleep under stars,
It would break behind bars.
And the question would echo,
Like a voice in your head:
*Would you allow this for your kids?*
Or would you stand instead?
Until you see every child as your own…
You’ve not understood love.