(INTRO)
shhh— load that code.
brain.exe in overload.
static breath — can’t feel no mode,
I write like wires in battle mode.
Tick-tick— pause — mind skip, replay.
Clock hand talk, but I don’t obey.
Glitch that thought, I bend cliché,
Words too sharp — they cut delay.
They code truth, I speak bug,
Half in love, half unplugged.
You rap sane — I rap shrug,
You write rhymes — I write drugs.
Ha! Brain spark, line arcs, aim off
— still mark!
Wrong note, right pitch, bass bite, full
spark.
Mind don’t talk — it hums in volts,
Every idea born with faults.
Break that beat — I skip my line,
Trip my word — it still sound fine.
I lose time but I gain design,
My error code? Divine sign.
I’m the glitch you can’t delete!
Hear my pulse beneath the beat!
Brain.exe — repeat, repeat,
Crash, revive, complete, complete.
Back to base, face half-lit,
Every thought got static grit.
Say I’m mad? I call it fit.
You dream normal — I dream split.
hah— breathe in noise, exhale math,
syntax bleed on the poet’s path.
word file cracked, I laugh,
mad genius — do the math.
shh… load complete.
memory clean.
system saved —
…but who saved me?
I’m the glitch you can’t delete!
Hear my pulse beneath the beat!
Brain.exe — repeat, repeat,
Crash, revive, complete, complete.