(Intro – whispered choir)
Before the spark, before the sound,
a calm that holds the turning ground.
Nothing moved — yet all began,
and stillness wrote the plan.
(Verse 1)
Galaxies drift like leaves in air,
each one drawn by silence there.
Every cause, every chain,
traces back where no change came.
(Pre-Hook)
No engine, no flame,
only order without a name.
(Hook)
The Unmoved Mover, center of the spin,
circle without start or end within.
All things flow, return, and blend—
motion born from what won’t bend.
(Verse 2)
Mountains fall and oceans rise,
time dissolves but reason lies
in symmetry that doesn’t fade,
the calm beneath the blade.
(Bridge – spoken over strings)
Every beat of every star
is distance from what things are.
All become, but One remains,
still heart inside the veins.
(Final Hook)
The Unmoved Mover, center of the spin,
axis where the worlds begin.
Through every change, it stays akin—
motion born from what won’t bend.
(Outro – choir + piano fade)
Before the spark, before the sound,
the Unmoved Mover turns the round.