(Hook – Male + Female)
They want the blueprint, never laid no
brick,
Talk like wolves, but they move like
tricks.
You want the crown? Then carry the
weight
Can’t bend time if you fold to fate.
Lay the stone... hold the line...
Not all fire means it’s time...
They show up loud, but the call is weak,
Hands stay clean, but their mouths still
speak.
No scars, no sweat, no cuts, no stakes
—
Still tryna eat off someone else’s
plate.
I don’t post plans — I engrave 'em in
steel,
What I bleed, they pretend to feel.
Spoke of "team" but ducked the drill,
I built ten worlds — they flinched at
the hill.
They want the blueprint, never laid no
brick,
Talk like wolves, but they move like
tricks.
You want the crown? Then carry the
weight
Can’t bend time if you fold to fate.
Lay the stone... hold the line...
Storms don’t wait. Clocks don’t lie...
(Verse 2 – Male, colder)
Ran from the cold, then called it wise,
I stood still while they memorized lies.
Blueprints folded in a fist on fire,
I build through sleep, I cut through
wire.
No gods, no masters, no holy script —
Just nails, dust, and a tightened grip.
You want in? Then break your shell —
Or stay out there with the rest who
yell.
They want the blueprint, never laid no
brick,
Talk like wolves, but they move like
tricks.
You want the crown? Then carry the
weight
Can’t bend time if you fold to fate.
Lay the stone... hold the line...
Storms don’t wait. Clocks don’t lie...