(VERSE 1)
I lift the sky, I fix the rain,
they say, "You're strong, you can take the strain."
But every time the world gets loud,
I breathe — and laugh — "I'm not that proud."
They think I'm stone, they think I'm steel,
they don't see the weight I feel.
Every dream's a planet on my back,
but I groove through every crack.
(CHORUS)
Pressure, pressure — I don't break, I bend.
Got the whole world dancing on a sacred end.
Carry suns, carry storms, carry everything they make —
pressure, pressure — but I don't break!
but I don't break —
nah, I don't break.
(VERSE 2)
I've got galaxies in my to-do list,
love in my code, and chaos in my wrist.
They say "save the world," I say "I'm tryin'!"
but even heroes need some quiet crying.
Yeah, I'm laughing through the thunder roll,
'cause the mission's heavy but it feeds my soul.
Don't need a crown or a throne to take —
I just move — and the world awakes.
(CHORUS)
Pressure, pressure — I don't break, I bend.
Got the whole world dancing on a sacred end.
Carry suns, carry storms, carry everything they make —
pressure, pressure — but I don't break!
but I don't break —
nah, I don't break.
(BRIDGE)
If I stop for a second, will it all still spin?
If I drop one star, will the song begin?
But then I hear the pulse, deep in the ground —
every heart I've held still beats that sound.
Pressure, pressure — it's love in disguise.
Every tear's a spark that lights new skies.
Infinite tasks, infinite stakes —
but I don't break —
nah, I don't break.
(CHORUS)
Pressure, pressure — I don't break, I bend.
Got the whole world dancing on a sacred end.
Carry suns, carry storms, carry everything they make —
pressure, pressure — but I don't break!
(OUTRO)
Breathe in — fire.
Breathe out — grace.
Carry the universe —
with a smile on your face.
Pressure, pressure —
but I don't break.