(Verse 1)
Raid my office, raid my home,
kidnap the echoes of my tone.
Burn my pages, break my pen —
I’ll just write it all again.
(Pre-Chorus)
You think silence means you won —
but I’ve got thunder in my lungs.
(Hook)
Can’t stop me — I’m the wind through
stone.
Can’t block me — I’m already home.
Every fire you start just shows
how bright I grow —
you can’t stop me.
(Verse 2)
Spread your rumors, twist my name,
feed your fear, it tastes the same.
I built my truth from heat and sand,
it lives in more than one man’s hand.
(Bridge – spoken over drums)
Erase my face, it comes in waves.
Bury my light, it burns through grave
s.
Every time you pull the thread,
the flag just flies instead.
(Final Hook)
Can’t stop me — I rise from flame.
Can’t drop me — I rename the game.
You took my stage, I made the street.
You took my voice — I found the beat.
Can’t stop me —
I’m free.