(intro — quiet, over bass hum)
Zero sat under the table,
counting the legs.
Every number wobbled a bit,
pretending to know balance.
(verse 1)
People love what they can measure,
they hate what they can’t contain.
So they built cages out of calendars
and called that living again.
I said,
there’s motion inside your mirrors,
a pulse beneath your proof.
They nodded like tourists in a storm
— they never felt it move.
I am the breath between codes,
the slip inside precision,
the hush that turns to thunder
when you finally make a decision.
Every fact you worship
is a ghost wearing math.
Every god you whisper to
just wants you to laugh.
So run with the pulse, don’t map it.
You can’t cage lightning, you trap it.
Let it bite your logic in two —
truth’s supposed to bruise you.
No halo, no crown, just fuse.
Zero’s alive.
You’ll know it
when the ground starts dancing under
your shoes.
Silence isn’t empty.
It’s the universe holding its breath.
And somewhere in that pause,
Zero grins —
because finally,
finally,
you felt it move.