(VERSE 1)
I never wanted the spotlight, I wanted the blueprint,
something solid underneath when the ground get thin.
While they argue colors for the outside view,
I'm counting load, stress, what the frame go through.
I seen dreams collapse from a weak foundation,
every big talk fail basic calculation.
Everybody wanna shine in the finished space,
nobody wanna stay when it's bricks and weight.
I don't draw lines just to make 'em look clever,
I draw lines so the whole thing last forever.
Pressure test every wall I design,
if it hold under doubt, it'll hold under time.
She say "slow down," I say "watch this,"
every move quiet but it all connect.
I don't rush highs, I respect the process,
that's how you turn chaos into progress.
I build when it's boring, I build when it's tense,
when nobody claps, I'm still in the fence.
They see the tower and think it appeared,
I see every night that it took to get here.
Yeah,
I don't need credit, I need it correct.
If it stand without me, I did it right.
I don't chase applause, I chase effect,
when they move inside it — that's success.
(PRE-CHORUS)
I'm the architect,
not of dreams, of weight.
Not of hype, of fate.
I don't talk — I calculate.
(CHORUS)
I'm the architect,
when it shake, I don't run.
I stay calm, adjust,
til the whole thing becomes.