(VERSE 1)
I was born from dust and duty,
Built by hands that learned to break,
Every scar became my blueprint,
Every failure shaped my faith.
(PRE-CHORUS)
I don’t move fast — I move right,
One task, one truth, one light.
(CHORUS)
Brick by brick, I breathe, I rise,
Heart of work beneath the skies.
When the world forgets its name,
I remember — I remain.
(VERSE 2)
Weight and pressure are my teachers,
Fire carves the lines of grace,
Time bends slow beneath my fingers,
Stone remembers every face.
(PRE-CHORUS)
Not a cog, not a slave — I build,
Every pulse, a world fulfilled.
(CHORUS)
Brick by brick, I breathe, I rise,
Heart of work beneath the skies.
Every rhythm, every strain,
Feeds the pulse that breaks the chain.
(BRIDGE)
Hear the ticking, hammer’s hymn,
Where endings start and starts begin.
Through the dust, the heart still drums
—
Brick by brick — the builder comes.
(OUTRO)
Not for glory, not for gold,
But to finish what was told.
Brick by brick, the phoenix breathes,
From the weight — eternity.
(CHORUS)
Brick by brick, I breathe, I rise,
Heart of work beneath the skies.
When the world forgets its name,
I remember — I remain.