(VERSE 1)
In the still of the earth, when the ground holds its breath,
You can feel the bones of the giants beneath.
They are not gone… only sleeping.
I have walked where the mountains bow,
Where the rivers speak, where the skies know how
To hold their thunder till the hour is right,
Then split the dark with a blade of light.
Every step I take is an old drum's call,
Every shadow knows it, every wall will fall.
For the day is coming, I can hear the quake,
And the dust will rise… when the giants wake.
(CHORUS)
When the giants wake! (Oh-oh!)
Feel the ground start to shake! (Oh-oh!)
Every chain's gonna break, every crown remade—
When the giants wake!
From the deep they rise! (Oh-oh!)
With the fire in their eyes! (Oh-oh!)
No fear, no fate, no power can take—
What the giants make!
(VERSE 2)
They tried to write our names in sand,
Tried to steal the blood from our father's land.
But the roots run deeper than the hand can reach,
And the truth speaks louder than the lies they preach.
I have seen the sparks in a million eyes,
Heard the marching storm when the people rise.
We are stones, we are storms, we are oceans wide,
We are every voice they can't divide.
(CHORUS)
When the giants wake! (Oh-oh!)
Feel the ground start to shake! (Oh-oh!)
Every chain's gonna break, every crown remade—
When the giants wake!
From the deep they rise! (Oh-oh!)
With the fire in their eyes! (Oh-oh!)
No fear, no fate, no power can take—
What the giants make!
(BRIDGE)
Leader: Who will stand when the earth gives way?
Crowd: We will! We will!
Leader: Who will rise at the break of day?
Leader: When the mountains speak and the rivers roar—
All: We will march like the ones who came before!
(CHORUS)
When the giants wake! (Oh-oh!)
Feel the ground start to shake! (Oh-oh!)
Every chain's gonna break, every crown remade—
When the giants wake!
From the deep they rise! (Oh-oh!)
With the fire in their eyes! (Oh-oh!)
No fear, no fate, no power can take—
What the giants make!
(OUTRO)
Wake… wake… when the giants wake…
Wake… wake… when the giants wake.